Contact

sharmashivank59@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shivank-dev (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Spring Boot React.js JavaScript

Shivank Sharma

Full Stack Engineer @ Cognizant || MERN Stack || Java || Spring || Hibernate || AWS

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

A Full Stack Engineer with 5+ years of experience in designing, and developing software products in an agile ecosystem by building scalable progressive web applications, Performance Optimization, Microservices, UI reusable components, and System Architecture.

Tech Stack

JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, Vue.js, Typescript, Nest.js, express.js, Redux, Lambda, API Gateway, Serverless Framework, Jest BDD & TDD, MySQL, NoSQL MongoDB, Cloud formation, Cloud watch, AWS, SES, SQS & SNS, Elastic search, Java, spring-boot.

Experience

Cognizant
Full Stack Engineer
November 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months)
Pune, Maharashtra, India

GryNow Influencer Marketing Web Developer July 2019 - February 2021 (1 year 8 months) Gurgaon, India

NEXTGN

Software Engineer June 2017 - June 2019 (2 years 1 month) Mathura Area, India

I am working on technologies such as Vue.js, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3,JavaScript, Bootstrap, IOS development with swift 3 and SQL.

Education

Dr. B. R. Ambedkar University, Agra
Bachelor of Science - BS - PCM, Mathematics · (2014 - 2017)

National Institute of Information Technology
GNIIT, Computer Software Engineering · (2014 - 2017)